Contact

andersleo05@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/anders-willard-leo (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Data Science Artificial Intelligence (AI) Machine Learning

Languages

Indonesian (Native or Bilingual)
English (Professional Working)
Chinese (Limited Working)

Certifications

Machine Learning Terapan

CS50's Introduction to Artificial Intelligence with Python

Belajar Pengembangan Machine Learning

IELTS

Belajar Machine Learning untuk Pemula

Honors-Awards

Silver Medal - Indonesia's National Olympiad in Informatics (OSN) 2022

1st Rank - Sutomo 1 Senior High School Programming Competition

Bronze Medal - SWEE (Sutomo World Education Expo) Mathematics Olympiad

3rd Rank - Find IT! Competitive Programming Competition

2nd Runner-Up - Google's Hackfest 2024 Hackathon

Anders Willard Leo

Building RISTEK | Computer Science Student at University of Indonesia

Depok, West Java, Indonesia

Summary

Anders is a first-year computer science undergraduate student at University of Indonesia. He has a strong passion for Machine Learning and Artificial Intelligence. In addition to his studies, he has been doing competitive programming since 2019.

Experience

RISTEK Fakultas Ilmu Komputer Universitas Indonesia Member of Data Science & Analytics SIG March 2024 - Present (5 months)

COMPFEST

Scientific Committee of Competitive Programming Competition March 2024 - Present (5 months)

Google Developer Student Club Universitas Indonesia Member

October 2023 - Present (10 months)

Parallax Coder

Co-Founder & Vice President of Program November 2022 - Present (1 year 9 months)

- Creating and developing programs
- Proactively evaluating progress of participants
- · Maintaining the overall integrity and effective quality assurance of the progam

BETIS Fasilkom UI
Staff of Academic and Tutoring
December 2023 - June 2024 (7 months)

Education

University of Indonesia

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science · (2023)

SMA Sutomo 1

High School Diploma, Science Stream · (2020 - 2023)